bighugelabs.com 2019-06-23

# BigHugeLabs.com Privacy Policy

## What This Privacy Policy Covers

  * This privacy policy pertains to the use of fd's Flickr Toys (the "Service") at bighugelabs.com.
  * This privacy policy covers how we treat personal information that the Service collects and receives. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number.
  * Children under 13 are not permitted to use the Service, and so this privacy policy makes no provision for children's use of the site.

## Information Collection and How it is used

### General Information

  * The Service collects personal information when you purchase products, sign in, or upload content.
  * If you would like to purchase products, we will ask for your address, email, phone number, and credit card information.
  * The Service automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie, and the page you request.
  * We use information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, research, and anonymous reporting.

### IP Addresses

IP Addresses are automatically reported by your browser each time you view a web page.

IP addresses may be used for various purposes, including:

  * To diagnose or service technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with the IP addresses controlled by a specific web company or ISP.
  * To tailor advertising based on geographic area or other information derived from your IP address. Aggregate information derived from IP addresses may also be reported to advertisers.
  * To estimate the total number of users visiting from specific geographical regions.
  * To make sure that people are not voting for themselves or friends during contests or promotions.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive.

  * You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set.
  * If you reject all cookies, you will not be able to use our products or services that require you to "sign in," and you may not be able to take full advantage of the service.
  * The Service uses its own cookies for a number of purposes, including to:
    * Access your information when you "sign in".
    * Keep track of preferences you specify while you are using the Service.
    * Estimate and report our total audience size and traffic.
    * Conduct research to improve our content and services.
  * The Service collects anonymous usage information through use of Google Analytics. Google Analytics may employ third party tracking cookies to gather anonymous browser, operating system, geographic, and website navigation information.
  * The Service uses Google AdSense to display advertising. The Service would not be able to stay in business without the revenue generated from advertising. AdSense uses third party cookies for frequency capping, aggregated ad reporting, and to combat fraud and abuse. Cookies are also used for personalized advertising which displays the most appropriate advertising banners based on your interests and activity. Personalized advertising is disabled and no personalized advertising cookies are used in the European Economic Area (EEA).

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

  * If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. The Service does not rent or sell your personal information.
  * Generally, the Service does not share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies without your consent except to provide products or services you've requested and in the following circumstances:
    * We may be required to disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas, warrants, court orders or legal process or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
    * It may be necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities, including without limitation, fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, or as otherwise permitted or required by law. We will transfer information about you if we are acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, we will notify you by email or by putting a prominent notice on the web site before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. We may share demographic information with business partners, such as "53% of users who regularly user the service are between 18 and 24" or the like. No personally identifiable information will ever be used without your permission (i.e. we will ask you for a quote or testimonial).

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may update this policy at any time for any reason. If there are any significant changes to how we handle personal information we will place a prominent notice on our site.

Effective Date: May 17, 2018
